RESUME

Name : MD. SAIF RAIHAN ASHRAF

Qualification: B.Sc Computer Science and Software Eng.

Email id : saif.raihan@9lenses.com / raihan.saif28@gmail.com

Mobile No : (+880) 1676332861

Address: 13/1, DMC West Nakhalpara, Tejgoan Dhaka

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

1 + years of Industry experience in providing User Interface & User Experience Design and Development with most usable enterprise wide applications. Specialized in full web site development, Front End Development.

Played a vital role in the Development of 9lenses Admin panel.

WORKING EXPERIENCE:

- Currently working as a Frontend Developer in 9LENSES, Dhaka from March 2013 to till date
- Working as a Software Engineer (Web) in ZS Solutions, Dhaka from Oct 2014 to till date.
- Worked as a **Front End Developer** in **Upwork** market place Bangladesh from 2010 to March 2013.
- Worked as a User Interface Engineer in Bhojnama (Mobile APP), Dhaka from June 2014 to Dec 2014.

SKILLS:

Web Technologies : HTML5, XHTML, CSS3, JavaScript/ jQuery/ Angular.is, Bootstrap,

Less/Sass, D3.js, Node.js / Bower / Grunt / Yeoman, WordPress.

Work flow & Delivery : Responsive Web Design, Mobile Development, Single app development,

Google Analytics

Works well in : PHP, ASP.NET, MySQL

App & Tools: Sublime, Web Strom, Git/SVN, Jira/Aha, Photoshop, Dreamweaver,

Illustrator, Fireworks

Others: Search Engine Optimisation (SEO).

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:

- Bachelor of Engineering in **Computer Science and Software Engineering** in April 2014 from American International University Bangladesh.
- Passed **HSC** in 2009 from Dhaka City Collage, Dhaka.
- Passed SSC in 2007 from G.L.H.S. School,

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Age & DOB : 23 years, 28-02-1992

Sex : Male

Permanent Address : Village: Thanahati,

Post Office: Raipura,

Narshingdi.

Languages Known : English, Bengali

I hereby declare that the above written particulars are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Place: Dhaka

Date: 05-05-2015 (MD. SAIF RAIHAN)